maxxandmore.com 2017-09-26

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**PH-ent operates the following websites:**  
tainster.com  
partyhardcore.com  
drunksexorgy.com  
allwam.net  
PissingInAction.net  
MadSexParty.com  
MyFetish.com  
FullyClothedSex.com  
CumSquad.com  
PeeSquad.com  
FullyClothedPissing  
PornstarsAtHome.com  
SlimeWave.com  
Tyrannized.com  
Orgymax.com  
Orgasmatics.com

**1.** PH-ent (the "website") applies the following Privacy Policy in order to protect your privacy. We understand your privacy is crucial to you.

**2.** We will let you know what information we may use and in what way we will be using it. The privacy policy applies to online activities done by you in PH-ent.

**3.** Changes: This policy may change from time to time. Please review the privacy policy periodically.

**4.** Information we may collect from you  
\- Personal information  
PH-ent may collect personal information in order to operate the website. this information may include, but is not limited to, email address, username, age, registration, purchase information, browsing history, search history,  
browser type, operating system, communication with other members within PH-ent, gender, zip code, postal code, city and country. Purchase details, browser type, operating system, browsing history and  
communications in the website are not disclosed anywhere. Other details may be disclosed on the website and reachable to other members in order to operate the website. Please note that we do not collect knowingly any  
personal information from users that are under the age of 18, as we require that all users represent upon registration that they are at least 18 years old.  
\- Cookies  
Cookies are small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while a user is browsing a website PH-ent may use cookies to keep track of your activity in the website. Cookies help us improve your  
experience on the website and give you the most optimized options, while protecting your account. Please note that if you choose to disable cookies tracking by changing the settings of your browser, this may restrict you from  
using some sections of the website.  
\- IP Address  
It is very common to collect IP address on e-commerce sites. This is done automatically each time you use PH-ent. In addition we collect the website you previously came from PH-ent. This is used to present you with the right  
options on the website. This information helps us to identify and optimize the service you are using.  
\- Information gathered by third parties  
Third party advertisers or partners on the PH-ent may also read cookies through their advertising or link placement. Please note that PH-ent does not control third party advertisers or links  
and their business practices and or privacy policies. 

**5.** Using the information we collect  
Your personal information is not shared with any third parties and is used mainly to communicate with you and provide you an optimized service. We mainly use this information to improve the services provided to you and present  
you with the correct options on the website. Also this information is used to deliver you, mainly through email and through your online account information and communication from other members or users. These  
communications are known as "Operational Communications." You can change your email preferences through your account and limit those emails. By creating a profile on the website you positively opt-in to receive  
messages from members and user in the website As well this information may be used to help you use the site, answer inquiries, solve problems and provide technical assistance.

**5.1** We may be required to share your information in order to operate the service successfully. Sharing may be required with our representatives and service providers so they can operate their service such as payment  
services, email services, customer service and promotional services. We request that those representatives and service providers do not to share or use your information for anything other than providing their service to the  
website.

**5.2** We may also use this information to present third parties with statistical information but this will not identify you personally.

**5.3** We may disclose your information if we are required to do so by a law enforcement agency or in case we need to use this information in order to enforce intellectual rights or resolve trademark issues.

**6.** Changing the information stored by our website  
You can modify your email preferences and opt-out from certain communications or change your personal information by updating your profile here. Please note that due to server synchronization updates, changes may take a few  
hours to appear on the website. You can also contact our customer service by clicking here or delete your account. The data will be saved by us but your profile will not be visible anymore.
